well life just keeps coming at you life
井井有条，不断前进你的生活
is as it's written here going to go
是因为它写在这里 要去
wrong just think of Joel now remember
错了只想到乔尔现在记得
the situation if you've got your Bible
你有圣经的情况
you might want to open up to job chapter
你可能想要打开工作章节
1 there's a man living in the Land of Oz
1有一个人住在绿野之地
and his name is Joe and the man was
而他的名字叫乔，那个人就是
blameless upright fearing God turning
无可指责的直立敬畏上帝转身
away from evil had seven sons and three
远离邪恶有七个儿子和三个 儿子
daughters his possessions were seven
女儿， 他的财产是七
thousand sheep three thousand camels
千羊三千骆驼
five hundred yoke of oxen that's a
牛五百枷锁，这是一个
thousand oxen five hundred female
千牛五百女
donkeys and very many servants and that
驴子和很多仆人
man was the greatest of all the men in
男人是所有男人中 最伟大的
the east and then as it text goes on the
东面 ，然后，因为它的文字那张
text tells us God's opinion of this man
文字告诉我们上帝对这个人的看法
Quran verse 6 there was a day when the
古兰经第6节有一天当时
sons of God came to present themselves
神的儿子来到了展示自己
before the Lord and Satan came along
在耶和华与撒但同来之前
with them when the Lord said to Satan
耶和华对撒但说的时候与他们同在
well where you been and Satan says well
还有你去哪里了撒旦说好
I've been roaming about on the earth
我一直在地球上漫游
walking around on it and the Lord said
走来走去，耶和华说
to Satan have you considered my servant
撒旦，你认为我的仆人
Joe there is no one like him on the
乔没有人喜欢他
earth blameless upright fearing God
地球无可指直的敬畏上帝
turning away from evil this is God's
远离邪恶，这是上帝的
opinion look at what God says have you
观点看看上帝对你说的话
seen my servant Joe there's not another
看到我的仆人乔没有另一个
guy like him down there who's blameless
像他一样的人在那里谁是无可指责的
and upright fears me walks with me turns
直立的恐惧我和我一起走
away from evil and what is Satan to say
远离恶事，什么是撒旦说
now who is Satan
现在谁是撒旦
Diablo's the devil he is the accuser of
暗黑破坏神是他的控告者
the Brethren he's a liar and what is he
弟兄他是个骗子，他是什么人
saying
话
well he doesn't serve you for nothing
他没有为你服务
look at what you've given him I mean I
看看你给他的东西，我的意思是我
mean read the text Lord seven thousand
意思是读七千神
sheep three thousand camels five hundred
羊三千骆驼五百
yoke of oxen five hundred female donkeys
牛枷五百只母驴
and lots of servants I mean the guy's
和很多仆人我的意思是那个人
got at all
得到了
wouldn't he serve you just take away his
他不会为你服务只是带走他的
stuff and you know he won't serve you
东西， 你知道他不会为你服务
and that's what Satan does if he gets a
这就是撒旦如果得到的话就会做的事情
chance to speak about you to God the
机会约你说话的神
Father he accuses you but he must have
父亲他指责你，但他必须
permission before he can touch you and
许可之前，他可以触摸和
so God says after Satan says you put a
所以上帝说撒旦说你放了一个
hedge around him in his house on every
每个人在他家里围着他对冲
side and you bless the work of his hands
一边，你祝福他的双手工作
and the possessions have increased but
并且财产有所增加但是
you put forth your hand and you touch
你伸出手去触摸
all he had and he will surely curse you
他所拥有的一切，他一定会诅咒你
to your face so then the Lord said to
你的脸是的话耶和华说：
Satan behold all that he has is in your
撒但看到他所拥有的一切都在你的身上
power but do not put your hand on him
但是不要把手放在他身上
so Satan departed from the with the Lord
所以撒但与主离开了
now I want you to pay attention as I
现在我想让你像我一样注意
read think about this two minutes in
读了想这两分钟
job's life look at what it says begin
工作的生活看看它开头说的是什么
reading with verse 14 so now on the
阅读第14节，所以现在
third verse 13 I'm sorry now on the day
第三节13我现在很抱歉
that his sons and his daughters were
他的儿子和女儿都是
eating in drinking wine in the oldest
在最古老的饮用葡萄酒中吃
brother's house a messenger came to Jobe
兄弟的房子是一个使者来到乔贝
and said the oxen were ploughing the
并说牛正在耕作
donkey's feeding beside them and the
驴子在他们旁边喂食
Sabian's attack and took them they also
萨比安的攻击并将他们带走了
slew the servants with the edge of the
杀仆人用的边缘
sword I alone have escaped to tell you
剑我一个人逃过来告诉你
and while he was speaking another also
同时他也讲另
came and said the fire of God fell from
来了，说上帝之火从那里落了下来
heaven and burned up the sheep and the
天堂烧毁了羊群
servants and consumed them and I alone
仆人和消费他们和我一个人
have escaped to tell you while he was
他曾经逃过来告诉你
speaking another came also and said the
说另一个也来了，并说
Chaldeans formed three bands and made a
迦勒底人组成了三支乐队并制作了一支乐队
raid on the camels took them and slew
对骆驼的袭击夺走了他们并且杀了他们
the servants with the edge of the sword
有剑边的仆人
I alone have escaped to tell you while
我一个人逃过来告诉你
he was speaking another came and said
他说话的另一个人来了
your sons and your daughters were eating
你的儿子和女儿都在吃饭
and drinking wine in the oldest
并在最古老的时候喝葡萄酒
brother's house behold a great wind came
兄弟的房子看到一阵大风来了
from across the wilderness struck the
从旷野穿过的地方
four corners of the house it fell on the
房子的四个角落落在了
young people and they died and I alone
年轻人和他们死了，我一个人
have escaped to tell you that
逃过来告诉你
took one minute to read I timed it and
花了一分钟时间阅读我的时间和时间
the text says one servant arrived while
文字说一个仆人到了
the other servant was talking in less
另一个仆人说话少了
than two minutes if you stretch it out
超过两分钟，如果你伸展出来
for the guys trying to get their breath
对于试图屏住呼吸的家伙们
while they're giving the message in less
虽然他们给的信息少了
than two minutes all is gone think about
所有人都想不到两分钟
it this man is the wealthiest man in the
这个人是这个人中最富有的人
7,000 sheeps she that's quite a heard by
她听说过7,000只羊
anybody standard or flock 3000 camels I
任何人标准或flock 3000骆驼我
understand for they go for a few
了解他们去了几个
thousand dollars apiece that's a lot of
一千美元，这是很多
cash 500 yoke of oxen 500 female donkeys
现金500牛牦牛500只母驴
and all his servants except the ones
以及除了那些以外的所有仆人
that brought the message and the Bible
带来了信息和圣经
tells us throughout the book of Job job
在整本工作书中告诉我们
loved his servants he loved those that
爱他的仆人，他喜欢那些
were serving him like his family and
正在服他像他的家人和
then his entire family is gone except
然后他的整个家庭都消失了
for his wife and at this point she
为了他的妻子，在这一点上她
doesn't become a help when she says well
当她说得好的时候不会成为一种帮助
why don't you just curse God and die you
你为什么不诅咒上帝而死你呢？
know and he has to say to her you're
知道，他必须对她说你
speaking as one of the foolish women
作为一个愚蠢的女人说话
would speak now life comes at you
现在会说生命来到你身边
you've been working all afternoon on a
你整个下午一直在工作
project on the computer and suddenly you
计算机上的项目突然间你
hit the button and it's the wrong button
按下按钮，这是错误的按钮
and it's all gone and you don't have a
它已经全部消失，你没有
hacker with you to get it back
黑客和你一起回来
and it's gone and you know that you're
它消失了，你知道你是
not supposed to be able to wipe it clean
不应该把它擦干净
and it's there someplace but you can't
它在某个地方，但你不能
get it and you know and that's really
得到它，你知道，这是真的
not that big of a deal that's not that's
不是那么大的交易不是那个
that's easy for me to say right okay but
这对我来说很容易说得对，但是
I've had it happen to me and trust me
我已经把它发生在我身上并相信我
compared to depression that's not that
与抑郁症相比，并非如此
big of a deal compared to the loss of
什么大不了的事相比，损失
your dad or mom that's not that big of a
你的爸爸妈妈或者这是没有那么大的
deal I was in New Jersey when the call
交易我在新泽西州打电话时
came we were on vacation and as I picked
来了，我们正在度假，因为我选择了
up the phone I didn't expect the news
打电话我没想到这个消息
but the associate pastor from the church
但教会的副牧师
say Bob you got to hear this I'm sorry
鲍勃说你听到这个我很抱歉
to have to call but Keith Gardner is
必须打电话，但基思加德纳是
dead what Keith garner is a physician's
死了凯斯加纳是医生的
assistant he's a young man what do you
助理他是个年轻人你是做什么的
mean he's dead
意味着他已经死了
he's got triplets and a young wife and I
他有三胞胎和一个年轻的妻子和我
mean everything was going well
意味着一切进行得很顺利
what what do you mean well there's a man
你的意思是什么，这是一个男人
who was coming to their clinic and he
谁来到他们的诊所和他
was getting medication and the doctor
正在接受药物和医生
who is over Keith had to say no more of
谁是在基思不得不说没有更多的
this medication you're misusing the pain
这种药物你是在滥用疼痛
medication and the man came back to the
药物和男人回来了
office and shot Keith and the doctor to
办公室和拍摄基斯和医生
death
死亡
life will come at you life is going to
生活会在你的生活将要
happen and life includes trials and the
发生，生活包括试验和
Word of God is really clear we are to
上帝的话语非常清楚我们要去
know Christ in Philippians chapter 3 in
在腓立比书第3章中了解基督
the power of his resurrection and in the
他的复活，并在电源
Fellowship of his sufferings and it says
他的苦难和他的团契说
to us in the book of Timothy any man who
在提摩太的书中给我们任何一个人
lives a godly life in Christ Jesus will
在基督耶稣的旨意中过一种敬虔的生活
suffer persecution and in Peter he tells
遭受迫害，在彼得他说
us in 1st Peter chapter 5 do not be
我们在1彼得前书5 不要
surprised by the fiery trial that
对火热的审判感到惊讶
surrounds you don't be so what and why
环绕你不是那么的，为什么
are we
是我们吗
why me no why now why this and we're
为什么我为什么现在为什么这和我们一样
surprised when we've been told no don't
当我们被告知没有时，我感到很惊讶
be surprised that suffering is going to
对痛苦感到惊讶
be there so now if you're gonna handle
如果你要处理，现在就在那里
this trouble and all the Hurricanes of
这个麻烦和所有的飓风
life and the 911s that come then you got
生活和你得到的911s
to go for the gold in the midst of your
去的黄金 之中的
trial if you look at your outline in the
如果你看看你的大纲，试用
left-hand column it says a job says in
左栏，它说工作说
chapter 23 but he God knows the way that
第23章， 但他知道那样的道路
I take when he has tried me I shall come
当他试过我的时候我会来，我会来的
forth as gold how do you get gold well
作为黄金，你如何获得黄金
it has to go through the fiery furnace
它必须通过火炉
in order to be smelted in order to be
为了被熔炼
prepared in order to be purified so when
为了被净化而准备的时候
I've gone through the trial I will come
我经历了试验，我将来
forth as gold because God is working
因为上帝在工作而成为金子
with me you could put along the side of
和我在一起你可以放在一边
that Philippians 1:6 you know there are
腓立比书1：6你知道有
no unfinished projects in God's garage
在上帝的车库里没有未完成的项目
he will complete the work he has started
他将完成他开始 的工作
in you and then of course in Romans 8:28
在你和然后当然 在罗马书8:28
the first thing to do if you're gonna go
如果你要去，首先要做的事情
for the gold and I know I misspelled
对于黄金，我知道我拼错了
gold I put two L's in it but had to do
黄金我把两个L'放在里面但必须这样做
that to make it work if you're gonna go
如果你要去，它会让它发挥作用
for the gold the first thing you have to
对于黄金的第一件事情，你必须
realize is God doesn't make any mistakes
意识到上帝不犯任何错误
he is too wise to make mistakes you have
他太明智了，不会犯错误
never heard God say whoops you've heard
从未听过上帝说你听过的呐喊
the story about the guy that was under
关于下得人的故事
local anesthetic for the for the
局部麻醉剂用于治疗
operation and as the doctor is operating
手术和医生正在运作
he can't see because of the sheet but
他无法看到，因为纸张的，但
all of a sudden the doctor says whoops
医生突然说哎呀
they know and and you know the patient
他们知道并且你知道病人
is there what do you mean whoops
那是什么意思哎呀
you know you're working on me all right
你知道你对我没事工作
now God never said that he never woke up
现在上帝从未说过他从未醒过来
in the morning read the newspaper and
早上看报纸和
said oh my I didn't know that was going
哦， 我说我不知道那是怎么回事
to happen last night
发生在昨晚
God is not surprised God is sovereign
上帝并不感到惊讶上帝是至高无上的
God is wife God has made a promise I
上帝是妻子上帝已经许诺了我
will
将
for those who love me work all things
对于那些爱我的人来说，做所有的事情
together for good for their good of
为了他们的利益而共同努力
coming to know me and being conformed to
来认识我并顺从
the image of Christ
基督的形象
and God is at work and then in second
上帝在工作，然后在第二
Corinthians first for 16 and 17
科林蒂安人首先是16岁和17岁
you got to operate with eternity sper
你必须用永恒的精子操作
spective when you are facing any trial
当你面临任何审判时，你都会嗤之以鼻
you you need to stop and say wait God is
你需要停下来说等上帝
in this God is in it for good God
在这里，上帝是为了善良的上帝
doesn't make mistakes
不犯错误
okay now eternities perspective let me
好吧，现在的eternities透视让我
put this in focus therefore we do not
把它放在焦点所以我们没有
lose heart but though our outer man is
尽管我们的外在人是，但我会失去信心
decaying at our inner man is being
我们内在的人正在腐朽
renewed day by day
日复一日
for momentary light affliction is
对于短暂的轻微痛苦是
producing for us an eternal weight of
为我们生产永恒的重量
glory far beyond all comparison so we've
荣耀远远超出所有比较所以我们已经
got to take and put eternity perspective
必须采取并提出永恒的观点
on this this trial is working an eternal
在这个试验中，这个试验是永恒的
weight of glory God is accomplishing
荣耀的重量正在成就
eternal purposes job could not see Satan
永恒的目的工作无法看到撒旦
in heaven talking to God accusing him
在天堂与上帝交谈指责他
all job saw was all the loss but how
所有的工作都看到了所有的损失，但如何
does Jill bruh spawned shall we receive
吉尔有没有bruh催生应收到
good at the hand of God and not
擅长上帝的手，而不是
adversity he understands what Paul said
逆境他明白保罗说的话
to the Philippians in the sense that if
对于腓立比人来说，如果
you live a godly life in Christ you will
你会在基督里过一种敬虔的生活
know him in the power of his
知道他的能力他的
resurrection and the Fellowship of his
复活和 他的团契
suffering somehow he knows that even
不知怎的，他甚至都知道
though he hasn't had the benefit of
尽管他一直没有 受益
seeing the cross and having the New
看到十字架和拥有新的
Testament epistles that have been
已有的遗嘱书信
written for our benefit that we have to
为了我们的利益书面我们必须
go by and so you must operate with
过去所以你必须经营
eternity sper spective that's not easy I
永恒的sper spective这不容易我
was working with the church work crew
正在与教会工作人员合作
and visalia then we had loaded a
和维塞利亚那么我们就装一
dumpster you know there there's a wide
垃圾箱， 你知道那里有广泛的
in there yay tall and we had thatched
在那里高高的，我们有茅草屋顶
the lawn at the church and this thing
在教堂的草坪和这件事
was loaded with all the fats we're
装满了我们所有的脂肪
moving it down the sidewalk to get it
沿着人行道向下移动它
back where it's supposed to be parked I
回到应该停放的地方我
was guiding the front end of it backing
正在指导它的前端支持
up three guys behind it pushing it I
我背后有三个人推着它
slipped my foot went under the wheel you
溜我的脚在车轮下，你去了
know they rolled it till I went on my
知道他们滚了它， 直到我继续我的
foot I yelled quite loud not realizing
脚我大声喊叫没有意识到
this was a momentary light affliction
这是一个短暂的轻微痛苦
but thinking
但是想一想
very heavy dumpster yell they stop you
非常沉重的垃圾桶叫喊他们阻止你
know and the next morning you know what
知道， 第二天早上你知道什么
text I was preaching on this one you
我正在讲这个你的文字
know and as I sat in a stool that
知道，当我坐在凳子上时
morning with my foot up on the side you
早上我的脚站在你身边
know I said that you know that did not
知道我说你知道没有
feel like a momentary light affliction
感觉像是一时的轻微痛苦
and it doesn't matter what it is it
并不要紧 它是什么，它
doesn't feel like a momentary light
感觉不像是瞬间的光
affliction that's why you need to
痛苦，这就是你需要的原因
operate out of eternity perspective
从永恒的角度来看
you've got to stop you have to think of
你必须停下来，你必须想到
this in the light of eternity and you
这与永恒和你有关
have to understand God is working an
必须明白上帝正在努力
eternal weight of glory through this
通过这种永恒的荣耀
trial I may not understand it now I will
审判我现在可能不会理解
some day I've got to operate with that
有一天，我必须与之合作
perspective next principle in terms of
透视下一个原则
this is live one day at a time
这是一次一天的直播
look at Matthew SiC it well note the
看看MatthewSiC吧
first Peter 3:14 passage as well but
第一次彼得3:14通过，但是
even if you should suffer for the sake
即使你应该为此而受苦
of righteousness you are blessed so even
正义你 甚至是幸运的
if you do right and then suffer for it
如果你做得对，然后为此受苦
because you get fired because you stood
因为你站起来因为你被解雇了
for what was right I just talked to a
对于什么是正确的我刚刚谈到了
man on the phone this week he's been
这个星期他一直在打电话的人
fired from three jobs in the last two
在最后两个职位中解雇了三个职位
years because he stood for righteousness
多年， 因为他代表正义
he's in the car trade and when he stood
他在汽车贸易中和他站立时
for what was right and said no you can't
对于什么是对的，说不，你不能
do that if you can't do that to the
如果你做不到这一点，那就去做吧
customer or you can't do that to the
客户或你不能这样做
other salesman you're not being fair to
其他推销员你不公平
them they said and we can do without you
他们他们说，我们没有你可以做
he stood for righteousness and he
他代表正义和他
suffered but in the eternal weight of
遭受了，但在永恒的重量
glory a weight of glory is being worked
辉煌荣耀的重量正在制定
in that so then live one day at a time
在那，所以然后一次住一天
Mathew 6:31 234 do not be anxious then
马太福音6:31234那时候不要着急
saying what shall we what shall we drink
说什么我们应该喝什么
or with what shall we close ourselves
或者什么，我们将自己封闭
for all these things the Gentiles
所有这些东西都是外邦人
eagerly seek just wait till Black Friday
急切地寻求等到黑色星期五
and you'll see them up there whoa they
你会看到他们在那里他们
will be looking for it big time for your
将为你寻找它的大时间
heavenly Father Knows you need all these
天父知道你需要所有这些
things but seek first his kingdom and
事情， 但首先寻求他的王国和
his righteousness and all these things
他的正义和所有这些事情
I'll be added unto you therefore do not
我会加入你们就当你不
be anxious for the mild tomorrow will
为明天的温和而着急
take care of itself look each day has
照顾自己每天看起来都有
enough trouble of its own live one day
有一天自己活得足够麻烦
at a time don't borrow from tomorrow you
一次不要从明天借你
don't have enough grace for tomorrow you
明天你没有足够的恩惠
look at somebody else's trial and say I
看看别人的审判然后说我
could never handle that well you're not
你永远不会处理得那么好
facing it so you don't need the grace
面对它所以你不需要恩典
they've got to handle it and God won't
他们必须处理它而上帝不会
give you grace for something you're not
给你优雅的东西，你不是
going through he gives you grace as you
经历他给你的恩典
need it in that situation so if you're
在那种情况下需要它，所以如果你是
not facing it
不面对它
there won't be grace to handle it and so
没有优雅处理它等等
you live one day at a time Lord what do
你一天生活一天，主做什么
I need today to do today now that does
今天我需要做的今天，现在，做
mean if there's a quiz next week and
意思是如果下周有一个测验而且
you're supposed to have read the
你本该读过的
material then one day at a time is
材料然后一天一次
reading the material today and reviewing
今天阅读材料和审查
the material the next day and reviewing
第二天的材料和审查
it each day until the test that's living
每天直到测试生活
one day at a time it's not what I'm not
有一天，在一个时间它不是什么我不
born for tomorrow and that's not till
明天出生，而不是直到明天
next Tuesday so I'm not gonna worry
下周二所以我不会担心
about reading it you know you know it's
关于阅读它你知道你知道它
it's that logical way of what is right
这是正确的逻辑方式
to do today and then living one day at a
今天做，然后在一天生活
time taking it that way and then the
时间采取这种方式，然后
second el in gold spell this way is to
第二EL黄金拼写这种方式是
look for a blessing in each day because
因为每天都在寻找祝福
in Philippians 4:8 it says finally
在腓立比书4：8中最后说
brethren if you want the peace of God
弟兄们， 如果你想要上帝的平安
that's being talked about in Philippians
这是腓立比人所谈论的
from verse 4 to verse 9 finally brethren
从第4节到第9节，最后是弟兄们
then put your mind on whatever is true
然后把你的想法放在任何真实的东西上
whatever is honorable whatever is right
什么是光荣的，无论什么是正确的
whatever is pure whatever is lovely
无论什么是纯粹的，可爱的
whatever is of a good repute there's any
无论什么是好的声誉， 都有
excellence of anything worthy of praise
卓越的任何值得赞美的东西
let your mind dwell on these things
让你的思想纠缠于这些事情
Philippians 4:6 and seven committed to
腓立比书4：6和7承诺
God with prayer and supplication and
上帝祈祷和恳求和
Thanksgiving peace of God will guard
上帝的感恩节安宁会守护
your heart then take your mind off the
你的心， 然后把你的思想从
problem and set your mind on the
问题并确定你的想法
goodness of God look for the blessing
上帝的良善寻求祝福
look for what God can teach you in this
寻找上帝可以教你的东西
circumstance look for how he can provide
环境看他如何提供
and you just look for a blessing what
你随便找 一个 什么样的祝福
can I thank God for in
我可以感谢上帝吗？
the midst of this day and in the midst
在这一天中间和中间
of that situation and then of course the
那种情况然后当然是
next point is do something for someone
下一点是为某人做点什么
else the idea here is that you need to
否则这里的想法是你需要的
reach out and minister to others Matthew
伸出援手并为其他人服务马修
25:40 and the king will answer and say
25:40国王回答说
to them truly I say to you to the extent
他们真的对我们说了一定程度
you did it to one of these brothers of
你是对这些兄弟中的一个做过 的
mine you did it to me in Matthew 7:12
我是你 在马太福音7:12 给了我的
therefore however you want to treat
因此， 你想要治疗
others so treat them for this is the law
别人这样对待他们，这是法律
and the prophets you minister to someone
以及你为某人服务 的先知
else how often I've gone as a pastor to
我是多久经常当牧师去的
the hospital ministered to somebody and
医院服务于某人和
they ended up ministering to me more
他们最终为我服务了更多
than I ministered to them as they spoke
比起 他们讲话时我所服侍的
to me of their situation and they
告诉我他们的情况和他们
ministered to me in that situation I
在那种情况下我服侍我
read the book when God weeps in the
当上帝哭泣时，读这本书
midst of the depression and I as I was
在萧条中，我和我一样
reading that book came to a certain
读那本书是肯定的
section and broke down in tears and one
一节又流下了眼泪和一个
of the things I hadn't been able to do
我无法做的事情
was they have really any emotions and I
他们真的有什么情绪吗？
just broke down in tears and I wept I
只是泣不成声，我哭了我
got down on my knees by the couch I
我躺在沙发上跪下了
prayed and I prayed with tears and I
祈祷，我和我一起哭泣祈祷
thought this is a breakthrough woke up
以为这是一个突破醒来
the next morning just as depressed as I
第二天早上和我一样郁闷
went to bed and I couldn't remember what
上床睡觉我记不起来了
I'd read in the book I had to go back
我在书中看到我必须回去
and read it again no you lose ability to
再读一遍，不要失去你的能力
concentrate you lose ability to really
集中你真的失去了能力
remember I couldn't remember I went back
记得我不记得我回去了
read it again but I was blessed by the
再读一遍， 但我很幸运
book so I wrote Johnny Erickson tada I
所以我写了Johnny Erickson tada I
think you know not ever expecting that I
以为你知道我没想到我
would hear back from her if I get this
如果我得到这个 ，她会收到她的回复
neat note back from her you know
她知道，从她那里回来的整齐的音符
thanking me for my note and giving me
感谢我的笔记和给我
some encouragement and in that she says
一些鼓励，她说
I'm going to be speaking at the Masters
我打算 在大师发言
College in November I'd really like to
十一月大学我真的很喜欢
meet you if you would come up after
如果你愿意，我会见你
chapel and we could talk together and so
小教堂，我们可以一起聊天等等
Chapel ended that morning and November
教堂在那天早上和十一月结束
and I waited for I don't know 30 minutes
我等了30分钟
she's talking to other people and I'm
她正和其他人说话，我
thinking well you know I'm not
好好想想你知道我不是
I'm not gonna keep her here any longer
我不会再把她留在这里了
she had mentioned before she spoke that
在她说话之前，她曾提到过
morning please pray for me especially
早上请特别为我祈祷
before I speak she did something like
在我说话之前，她做了类似的事情
what I've done with each of the sessions
我每次会议都做了什么
but she said I really need God's help
但她说我​​真的需要上帝的帮助
this morning I am really more than usual
今天早上我比平常更多
sensitive of my own weakness and so she
敏感的是我自己的弱点，所以她
and with that in mind and she's been
考虑到这一点，她一直都是
visiting for 30 minutes I her husband
我丈夫来访30分钟
was there and I said to him you know
在那里，我告诉他，你知道
what would you tell Johnny that I was
你会告诉约翰尼我是谁？
here but I don't want to keep her here
在这里，但我不想让她留在这里
longer and he said oh no no your Bob
更长，他说哦，不，不，你的鲍勃
Somerville she wants to talk to you you
萨默维尔，她想跟你说话
need to wait she wants to talk to you so
需要等待，她想和你谈谈
I waited and so then we spoke and as we
我等了，然后我们和我们说话
spoke one of the things she said to me
她说了一句她对我说的话
was Bob what if your feelings never come
鲍勃是鲍勃，如果你的感情永远不会来
back see I had to thank God for my
回来看我必须感谢上帝
paralysis and I had to say to the Lord
瘫痪，我不得不对主说
Lord I'm willing to live with the new
主啊，我愿意和新人一起生活
normal
正常
Bob are you willing to live with the new
鲍勃，你愿意和新人一起生活
normal if your feelings don't ever come
如果你的感情永远不会来，那是正常的
back Paul you know that's you know
保罗你知道那是你知道的
that's straightforward counsel and I
那个直截了当的忠告和我
wasn't sure I really wanted to answer
我不确定我真的想回答
that question but you know when you're
这个问题，但你知道什么时候你
taking that from somebody that's been in
同时，从别人那一直在
the NFL of suffering for 42 years and
美国国家橄榄球联盟的痛苦已经42年了
she's speaking from that wheelchair you
她从轮椅上来讲你
listen that's why the book when God
听那就是为什么这本书当上帝
weeps she doesn't sidetrack any of the
哭泣她不会偏见任何一个
stuff he's dealing with some of the
他正在处理的一些事情
hardest issues that are there to deal
那有没有处理最棘手的问题
with and so I had to answer that
有， 所以我不得不回答这个问题
question and then as we kind of finished
问题，然后我们完成了
our conversation I said well how can I
我的谈话我说得怎么样
pray for you well says you can pray this
为你祈祷说你可以祈祷
has been a really rough year she's
她 是一个非常艰难的一年
dealing with cancer she was taking chemo
处理她正在服用化疗的癌症
she had phantom pain she had pain where
她有痛苦的幽灵疼痛在哪里
she wasn't supposed to have pain they
她不应该有痛苦
gave her medication for it and the
她给了药和药
medication was making her depressed and
药物让她感到沮丧
her thinking and so on and she wasn't
她的想法等等，她不是
appreciating that so she just stopped
欣赏， 所以她只是停下来
the medication said I'd rather doodle
药物说我宁愿涂鸦
with the phantom pain than deal with
与幻肢痛不是处理
what this man
这个男人是什么
Asian is doing to me and been through
亚洲人正在对我做并经历过
all of that stuff a lot and then I said
所有这些东西很多，然后我说
well what are you where are you headed
那你在哪里，你在哪里
when you go home today so while going
当你今天回家，所以，当去
home we're gonna take a rest and then we
我们要休息一下，然后我们
get on a red-eye at a midnight down at
午夜时分，目瞪口呆
LAX and we're going I believe it was
洛杉矶和我们要去，我相信它是
Guatemala
危地马拉
we're in do five days of ministry with
我们在做五天的事工
the handicapped and she's in a sense
残疾人和她在某种意义上
barely back on her feet from the bouts
几乎没有从比赛中站起来
that she's been having with a cancer in
她一直有与癌症
that stuff and you know my thought was
那些东西，你知道我的想法
Somerville you are a wimp dog mama's boy
萨默维尔你是一个懦弱的狗妈妈的男孩
you don't understand anything about
你什么都不懂
suffering you think this stuff you've
痛苦的你会想到这些东西
been through is something this lady's in
经历过这位女士的事
the NFL and God is using her and so I
NFL 和上帝正在使用她，所以我
prayed for her and I pray for her you
为她祈祷，我为她祈祷你
know more often maybe than any other
比任何其他人更了解
what we would call you know well-known
我们所谓的你知道的是众所周知的
leaders because of the ministry that God
领导因为上帝的事工
has given to her but what is that
已经给了她但是那是什么
ministry come from she's certainly going
事工来自她肯定会去
for the gold she's living one day at a
对于黄金，她有一天住在一个
time she's trusting God to give her the
她相信上帝给她的时间
strength that he can give her and she's
他能给予她和她的力量
doing things for others she's reaching
为她正在接触的其他人做事
out to others and God is at work in her
对别人说，上帝在她身上工作
life alright then secondly or be in our
生活还好，其次是或在我们的
outline follow a plan that'll give hope
概述遵循计划，会给 希望
in every trial I give credit here to a
在每次试验中，我都会在这里给予赞誉
speaker named Bill Gothard I ascended
名叫Bill Gothard的演讲者我升天了
one of his basic youth conflict seminars
他的一个基本青年冲突研讨会
back in 1971 or 72 and this basic five
早在1971年或72年，这个基本五
point stood out to me and so I've taken
点突出了我，所以我采取了
those five points and worked my own
这五点并且是我自己的
outline around it but the five points
围绕它勾勒出五点
come from that conference that I
来自那次会议，我
attended back in 1970 and number one in
1970年回国，第一名
this and you want to think ahead to the
这一点，你要提前想的
diagram that's at the bottom of your
在你的底部的图表
outline this diagram asking the question
概述此图提出问题
what can I learn and the fruit of the
我有什么可以学习的水果
Spirit but you have God at the top and
精神， 但你有上帝和上帝
then number one is acknowledging that
然后排名第一的是承认这一点
God is sovereign
上帝是至高无上的
number two is don't grumble or complain
第二个是不要发牢骚或抱怨
number three is thank God
第三是感谢上帝
number four is asked if God is
第四个问题是上帝是否
disciplining you for anything and number
训练你做任何事情和数字
five is asking the question what can I
五是问我有什么问题
learn so backing up now to point number
学习如此备份到现在的点数
one but we're working our way around the
一个，但我们正在努力
that triangle is this acknowledge that
这个三角是这个承认
God is sovereign Lee working all things
上帝是主权李工作的一切
together for good we're back to this
我们一起回到这里
point that we've been on you know over
点，我们一直在你知道了
and over and over again God is at work
一遍又一遍，上帝在工作
God doesn't have a problem taking
上帝没有问题
responsibility some of us you know we
我们中的一些人，你知道我们
don't we we we've got to be sure that we
我们不是，我们必须确定我们
get God off the hook you know like the
让上帝摆脱困境， 就像你知道的那样
minister in Wales when a mudslide or
威尔士部长在泥石流或泥石流时
sludge slide came down the mountain and
污泥幻灯片来到从山上下来，
wiped out a school and killed the young
摧毁了一所学校并杀死了这个年轻人
people in that school and if they kind
在那所学校的人，如果他们是善良的
of said well God you know must have been
的说好神，你知道一定是
you know he just wasn't aware or he
你知道他只是不知道或他
couldn't really have prevented that and
不能真正阻止这一点，
we're trying to get God off the hook
我们试图让上帝摆脱困境
well Exodus 4:11 the Lord says to Moses
出埃及记4:11 耶和华对摩西说
look who made man's mouth or who makes
看看是谁制造了男人的嘴巴或是谁制造的
him mute or death or seeing or blind is
他静音或死亡，或看到或失明
it not I the Lord when the disciples
门徒们，这不是我的主
come out of the temple and they see the
从寺庙出来，他们看到了
guy there and he's blind and they say
那里的家伙，他是盲人，他们说
Lord oh why is he blind his sin or his
主啊，为什么他瞎了他的罪或他的罪
parents in they've got the same problem
他们的父母也遇到了同样的问题
job's counselors had and you know it's
工作的辅导员已经知道了
got to be something the closet here it
必须成为这里的壁橱
was at him and his sin or was it his
是在他和他的罪或是他的
parents and Jesus says what neither but
家长和耶稣所说的话，但都不
that the works of God might be made
可以创造上帝的作为
manifest in him
在他身上显现
diamonds in the dust the idea that how
钻石在尘埃中的想法如何
do you display a diamond against black
你在黑色上展示钻石吗？
because it then sets off the reflections
因为它然后引发了反射
of the diamond how do you get a diamond
钻石如何获得钻石？
you cut it so that it reflects light
你切它，以便它反射光
from any angle but cutting is hard iron
从任何角度来看，切割都是硬铁
sharpens iron and sparks fly
锐化铁和火花飞
and so God is at work and he takes
所以上帝在工作，他需要
responsibility and he says I will work
责任，他说我会工作
all things together for good and Genesis
所有事情都是好的和创世纪
5:20 the the evil that you intended God
5:20 你想要上帝的邪恶
intended for good what you intended for
旨在实现您的目标
evil Joseph says to his brothers God
邪恶的约瑟夫对他的兄弟上帝说
intended for good now listen to this
打算好好听听这个
carefully the sovereignty of God and the
认真对待上帝和上帝的主权
Marvel of the sovereignty of God working
惊叹上帝工作的主权
all things together for good does not
所有的事情都是好的，不是
take away the hurt it's there and it's
带走伤害它的存在和它的
real so when mom is 99 actually she was
真的， 所以当妈妈99岁的 时候 她真的是
yes she was 99 she would be turning 100
是的，她99岁，她将100岁
within a few weeks of when not this
在没有这个的几个星期内
happen and we went to visit her and to
发生了，我们去拜访了她
help take care of her for two weeks with
帮忙照顾她的两个星期
my sister who was caring for her at that
我的姐姐谁是那个照顾她
time and she's gone to bed but I hear
时间和她上床睡觉但我听到了
her crying well mom takes out her
她哭泣的妈妈把她拿走了
hearing aids she doesn't hear kind of
助听器，她没有听到那种
how maybe loud she is and I went out and
她是多么大声，我出去了
I got down by her bed and I said mom
我躺在她的床边，我说妈妈
what's the matter but she just thought
什么事情，但她只是想
Oh Robert I didn't intend for you to
哦罗伯特我不打算你
hear and I said well it's okay but
听到，我说好了，但是
what's the matter I just want to go home
怎么回事我只想回家
to be with Jesus life was a tremendous
与耶稣同在， 生活是巨大的
struggle at that point and that the
在这一点上和斗争
recognization of the sovereignty of God
认识到上帝的主权
doesn't take away from the difficulty
不从困难带走
and the hardness and that the the issues
且硬度与该问题
of what you're going through and you
你正在经历的事情和你
know you know the little ad you see in
知道你知道你看到的小广告
the when you go to get something done
什么时候去完成某件事
and they have that little cartoon up
他们有那个小卡通片
there that you know a crisis on your
在那里， 你知道你的危机
part does not necessarily mean a crisis
部分并不一定意味着危机
on my part you know you should have
就我而言，你知道你应该拥有
brought this stuff sooner you know I'm
你很快就知道我带来了这些东西
not gonna get a little upset about this
拿不到 这个 有点不高兴
just because you are but you know the
只因为你是，但你知道
definition of minor surgery and major
小手术和专业的定义
surgery you all know that don't you you
手术你们都知道，不是你们
know minor surgeries anything they do on
知道他们做的任何小手术
you major surgeries any
你是主要的手术室
they do I mean so when you're in the
他们的意思是，当你在这里时
trial its major surgery and you've got
试验它的大手术而你已经得到了
to realize as a counselor you may be
你可能会成为一名顾问
thinking what this is nothing you know
想什么，这不是你知道的
Johnny Erickson tada could have said to
约翰尼·埃里克森田田可能到说
me Bob suck it up what you're facing
我鲍勃吮吸你所面对的
isn't really that bad but she didn't do
并不是那么糟糕，但她没有这么做
that she just asked me a hard question
她刚问我一个难题
are you willing to live if that's the
你愿意活下去吗？
new normal for the glory of God so I've
上帝荣耀的新常态，所以我
got to recognize though and when you
不过要认识到你
recognize that though that brings hope
认识到这虽然带来希望
ah but what do we usually do
啊，但我们通常做什么
oh girl mo complain and the word their
哦，女孩莫抱怨和他们的话
guru so must me it sounds like what it
大师所以我必须听起来像它
says you know no grumbling o somos you
说你知道没有抱怨你
know you're muttering to yourself you
知道你喃喃自己，你
are complaining you know why me why now
抱怨你知道为什么我为什么现在
why this you know how in the world is
为什么你知道这个世界是怎样的
this ever gonna work out for good you
这对你有好处
know and as we talked about it yesterday
知道并且我们昨天谈到了它
do all things without grumbling and
做所有事情，不要抱怨和
complaining and we do all things with
抱怨，我们做所有事情
grumbling and complaining somehow
不知何故抱怨和抱怨
there's a there's a translation that's
有一个有一个翻译这
wrong here that out should be gone you
这里错了，应该离开你
know it's not without its with that's
知道它不是没有它的
what we do that's how we react that's
我们这样做是我们如何做出反应的
what happens bummer you know metal
你知道金属会发生什么事让人失望
sticks oh man you know and they're all
坚持哦，你知道的男人，他们都是
Christian curse words but remember it's
基督徒诅咒的话， 但要记住它
the intonation it's the attitude of your
语调是你的态度
heart it is the the way that you are
心脏是的，你现在 的样子
responding and again what are you doing
回应又是你在做什么
it doesn't sound that's bad but actually
听起来不是很糟糕但实际上并不好
you are shaking your fist in the face of
你面对的是握拳
God and you are saying god I know better
上帝，你说的是上帝，我知道的更好
how to handle this day than you do look
如何处理这一天比你看
at what you've let happen rather than
在你所发生的事情而不是
proverbs 16 says mind a man plans his
谚语16说，一个人计划他的
way is it good to make plans well sure
如何制定计划是很好的
you don't leave your brains at the door
你不要把你的大脑留在门口
when you become a Christian God expects
当你成为基督徒时，上帝期待
you to plan but then it says the Lord
你计划但是然后它说主
directs your steps I made a plan 16
指导你的步骤我制定了一个计划16
things on the list what I'm gonna get
列表上的东西我会得到什么
done today and I've got plenty of time
今天完成，我有充足的时间
to do them all and I haven't gotten one
做所有这些，我还没有得到一个
done yet
完成了
because God has directed my steps he has
因为上帝指示了我的步伐
blueprinted over my plan
我的计划蓝图
and I should be saying thank you lord
我应该说谢谢主人
thank you lord thank you lord that's
谢谢阁下，谢谢你，主啊
what I should be saying that's the step
我应该说的是这一步
that we need to come to we need to
我们需要达到这个目标
rejoice in your problem we need to say
为我们需要说的问题感到高​​兴
thank you for it now this is really
谢谢你，现在这是真的
important and in your resources there's
重要的，在你的资源有
a book by Mae Bailey and faith is not a
Mae Bailey的一本书和信仰不是一本书
feeling choosing to take God at His Word
感觉选择接受上帝的话语
and she just kind of nails this and
她只是指着这个和那个
drives it home in this whole book count
驾驶它的家在这整本书计数
it all joy when you fall into various
当你陷入各种各样时，这一切都是快乐
trials have any accountants in the room
审判在会议室有任何会计师
any accountants got the wife of an
任何会计师都得到了一个
accountant I know some place okay all
会计师我知道有些地方都还好
right so you you know what counted all
对，所以你知道什么是全部
joy
喜悦
what does that mean added up to be a joy
这意味着什么加起来是一种快乐
God is in this God is in it for good
上帝在这里，上帝永远在其中
therefore I give things I add it up and
因此我给出了我添加的东西
when I add it up I get things it's not
当我把它添加起来时，我发现事情并非如此
the old Toyota commercial you know you
旧的丰田商务，你知道你
know Whoopi you jump up and click your
知道Whoopi你跳起来然后点击你的
heels I got a Toyota you know that's
高跟鞋我有一辆你知道的丰田
that Toyota feeling well it's not bad I
丰田感觉很好，我也不错
am NOT happy about the herniated disc I
我对椎间盘突出不满意
still have in my back and the fact that
仍然在我的背后和事实
I can't lift more than 20 pounds and the
我不能举起超过20磅的
fact that I have to ask my wife to come
事实上，我必须要求我的妻子来
and we have to pick up the suitcase
我们必须拿起行李箱
together and then put it in the trunk
一起然后把它放在行李箱里
you know that doesn't really make me
你知道这并没有真正让我受益
feel like a man I don't like it if I
感觉像个男人我不喜欢它，如果我
have to ask the person you know
不得不问你认识的人
especially if it's a lady that you know
特别是如果你知道这是一位女士
can you take the groceries out because
你可以把杂货，因为
the bags are heavier than I'm supposed
袋子比我想象的要重
to live and you know that doesn't make
生活，你知道，没有
me feel like a man it makes me feel like
我觉得自己像个男人，让我感觉像
the WIMP dog mama's boy that I mentioned
我提到的WIMP狗妈妈的男孩
before okay but it's part of where I am
好之前，但这是我的一部分
so I am supposed to add that up to be a
所以我应该补充一点
joy
喜悦
why because God's in it to develop
为什么因为上帝在其中发展
perseverance to bring completion into my
坚持不懈地完成我的工作
life and then the first Thessalonians of
生活， 然后是第一个塞萨洛尼亚人
5:18 everything give thanks for this is
5:18一切都要感谢
God's will for you in Christ Jesus I
上帝 在基督耶稣里对你的旨意我
mean I know God's will for your life and
意思是我知道神的旨意，为您的生活和
I'm not that smart
我不聪明
but I can read the text in everything
但是我可以在所有内容中阅读文本
give
给
for this is the will of God for you in
因为这是上帝对你的旨意
Christ Jesus and everything not some
基督耶稣和一切都不是
things not most things not many things
事情并非大多数事情并不多
not almost all things you give things
几乎没有你给的东西
you give it as a sacrifice to God in
你把它作为一个祭祀神
your notes following it says at the
你的笔记跟着它说的
bottom of your notes on the page to
在页面上的笔记底部
their study Psalm 50 14 and 23 and 54 6
他们的研究诗篇50 14 14和23和54 6
and 116 17 they all talk about the
和116 17他们都谈
sacrifice of praise why is it called a
赞美牺牲为什么叫一
sacrifice of praise it's a sacrifice of
牺牲赞美这是对它的牺牲
praise when you thank God for an issue
当你感谢上帝的一个问题时，你会称赞
that would normally be a problem why
通常会是一个问题，为什么
because you're doing that by faith you
因为你是凭信心做到的
see if I walked around the room this
看看我在房间里走了 这
morning or this afternoon and I gave you
早上或今天下午，我给了你
all a $20 bill and said thanks for
所有20美元的账单，并表示感谢
coming you'd all say oh thanks dr. Bock
来吧你们都说哦谢谢博士。博克
oh this is costing him a good deal of
哦，这让他付出了很多代价
money and you know take a friend out to
钱，你知道带一个朋友出去
eat you know gonna have to be not an
吃你知道必须不是一个
expensive restaurant what's 20 bucks for
昂贵的餐厅什么是20美元
two of you but you know take a friend
你们两个，但你知道带朋友
out to eat and just enjoy thanks for
出去吃饭，只是感谢你
coming I imagine most of you would say
即将到来我想你们大多数人会说
thank you you know your mama taught you
谢谢你，知道你的妈妈教过你
to say thank you
说谢谢
and you'd say thank you that's really
而且你会说谢谢你真的
neat on the other hand if I said all the
另一方面，如果我说了所有的话，整洁
doors are locked and there's guys out
门被锁了，有人出门了
there three times the size of Bruges you
布鲁日 的面积是你的三倍
know and they're mean they're ugly but
知道，他们的意思是他们很难看但是
they do have little machines you can
他们确实有很少的机器
slide your credit card or you can give
滑动你的信用卡或你可以给
them an extra 20 bucks but I've decided
他们额外20美元，但我已经决定了
that you know I need a little extra cash
你知道我需要一点额外的现金
and you're gonna have to pay that before
并且你得 支付之前
you get out well if the guys are big
你走出好，如果球员是大
enough and mean enough and look like
足够和足够的意思和看起来像
they might do nasty things to you you're
他们可能会做坏事。你你
gonna pay 220 bucks and then you really
要支付220美元，然后你真的
complain to Bruce and Wayne about who is
向布鲁斯和韦恩抱怨谁是谁
this coo coo asked here but it's a trial
这个咕咕咕咕地问这里，但这是一个试验
it's easy to say thank you when God
当上帝很容易说谢谢你
gives you something extra something good
给你一些额外的好东西
something that's obviously good but when
什么东西显然是好的，但什么时候
God gives you a trial which he has
上帝给你一个他有的试炼
promised to work for you're good now you
承诺为你 工作 现在好
have to exercise faith in order to give
必须运用信仰才能给予
things but
事情但是
as you exercise faith that then is how
当你运用信心，那就是如何
you please God because Hebrews 11:6 says
你喜欢上帝， 因为希伯来书11：6说
without faith it is impossible to please
没有信心就不可能取悦
God and I don't have the Hebrews 11:6
上帝和我没有希伯来书11：6
reference in there but you ought to add
在那里引用，但你应该补充
that in there in terms of thanking him
在那里感谢他
by faith and then the next step is ask
凭信心然后下一步就是问
God could God be disciplining me for sin
上帝可以让上帝为了罪而训练我
Here I am I'm in this situation could
我在这里，我在这种情况下可以
God be disciplining me for sin well you
上帝要为你惩罚我的罪
know for example if you go to the men's
例如， 如果你去男人那就知道了
golf tournament and you know it's the
高尔夫锦标赛，你知道它是
it's Visalia and you know yesterday it
这是维萨利亚，你昨天就知道了
was 70 today it's a hundred and you know
今天是70岁，你知道的是一百
at the end of the first nine holes you
在前九洞结束时你
have a Pepsi and at the break when you
有百事可乐和在休息的时候你
hit the the golf course deal you have
打了你所拥有的高尔夫球场优惠
another Pepsi and then when you get to
另一个百事可乐然后当你到达
the end of the courts you have a Pepsi
法院的你到底有百事可乐
and then when they we are doing our
然后当他们我们做我们的时候
little thing together as a lunch you
小东西在一起作为你的午餐
know they don't really have any thing
知道他们真的没有任何东西
that you're interested in so you have
你有兴趣，所以你有
iced tea and then go right from there
冰茶，然后从那里去
more or less to a graduation for one of
或多或少为一毕业
the men from the church who's completed
来自教会的人已经完成了
his physical therapy degree and you know
他的物理治疗学位，你知道
you have some more tea and another Pepsi
你有更多的茶和另一个百事可乐
and then about 10 o'clock
然后大约10点钟
suddenly you have serious muscle cramps
突然你有严重的肌肉痉挛
by the time you get to the hospital you
当你到医院的时候
were talking through your teeth because
因为你的牙齿在说话
you can't open your mouth because your
你不能张嘴，因为你的
jaw is frozen like this and that's the
下巴被冻结这样，这就是
question Lord could you be disciplining
问题主你能训练吗？
me for something yes you idiot you drink
我是因为你喝酒的白痴
nothing but caffeinated drinks all day
一整天都没有含咖啡因的饮料
you had no water they dehydrate you
你没有水让他们脱水
so there's a sin there I stupidly
所以我愚蠢地犯了罪
treated my body I didn't even think
对待我的身体我甚至没有想到
about it okay but the first thing that
它不错，但第一件事，
came to my mind when I'm laying in the
来到我的脑海里，当我在我铺设
hospital you know you know three IV bags
医院你知道你知道三个IV袋
later I went home I didn't preach the
后来我回家了，我没有传教
next morning but
第二天早上但是
you know it wasn't that serious but you
你知道这不是那么严重但是你
know I don't make that mistake again
我知道我不会再犯这个错误
those drinks dehydrate you they do not
那些饮料让你脱水，但他们没有
hydrate you watered us and so you need
保湿你给我们浇水，所以你需要
water and so you know okay is God
水，所以你知道上帝是好的
disciplining me and their sin for
管教我，他们的罪
instance I walk out of the house I shut
比如我走出房子我关的
the door firmly behind me you could say
你可以说 ，门紧紧围绕在我身后
I slammed it but let's just say I showed
我猛烈抨击但是我只是说我表现出来了
it firmly behind me now this is when we
它坚定地落后于我，现在这就是我们
lived in Teaneck New Jersey and so it's
住在新泽西州的蒂内克，所以就是这样
November and the storm window is in the
11月和风暴窗口在
outside door has lower solid upper is
外门有较低的实心鞋面
either a screen or a storm window and
无论是屏幕还是风暴窗口
the storm window drops out and so what
暴风雨的窗户熄灭了
does Bob do he complains lord then and
鲍勃会不会抱怨主人呢？
say lord I just said no my goodness I'm
说主我只是说我没有善意
strong windows falling out
强大的窗户掉了出来
stupid storm window I'm gonna have to
愚蠢的风暴窗口， 我将不得不
spend the who knows how much time to fix
花谁知道需要多少时间来修复
the dumb thing this is really stupid I
愚蠢的事我真的很蠢
got lots of things to do this afternoon
今天下午有很多事要做
I don't have time for this problem and
我没有时间解决这个问题
God brings to mind the first count Adele
上帝让人想起阿黛勒的第一个伯爵
Joel we didn't fall into various trials
乔尔，我们没有陷入各种考验
and I think Lord this I didn't fall into
我认为主啊，我没有陷入其中
this trial the dumb window fell out this
这个试验的哑窗掉了下来
is really stupid you mean I'm supposed
真的很蠢你的意思是我应该的
to apply this verse to the little things
这节经文，适用于小事情
like this and the Lord you know as he
像这样和主，你知道他
uses the word brings the thought to mine
使用这个词带来了我的思想
well is that what the verse says are you
这节经文对你说的是好的
gonna keep grumbling which you know is
要保持你所知道的抱怨
sin or are you gonna thank me for the
罪恶或者你会感谢我的
trial Lord it seemed so stupid but okay
审判主看起来很蠢，但没关系
Lord thank you for the trial next
主啊，谢谢你接下来的审判
question could you be disciplining me
问题你能训练我吗？
for anything well why did you shut the
为什么你关闭了
door so firmly because I was upset with
门如此坚定，因为我被打乱
my wife and what did you say to your
我的妻子，你对你说了什么
wife before you left well that was rude
你离开之前妻子 很粗鲁
and unkind my tone of voice was harsh
和不友好我说话的语气很恶劣
and my voice was raised because she
我的声音因为她而被提高了
doesn't agree with me and you know it's
不同意我，你知道的
back to that same thing and I would have
我会回到同样的事情
agreed with her but then we was both
同意她，但后来我们都是
been wronged you remember that okay you
被冤枉你还记得 你好吗
got to get some important things here
得到了一些重要的东西在这里
from the conference all right and so you
从会议的所有权利，所以你
know I said okay Lord that was sin so I
知道我说好的主那是罪，所以我
went back after confessing to him and
在向他承认之后回去了
said honey I was rude I was
亲爱的我说我很粗鲁
kind I raised my voice and I made light
我提高了声音，然后我发光了
of your opinion all that was sin will
你认为一切都是罪恶的意志
you forgive me so when you ask
当你问的时候，你原谅我
forgiveness we ought to be precise and
宽恕我们应该是精确的
take responsibility for what we did but
对我们所做的事负责
is God disappoint what could be now you
是上帝让你失望了
see again once you say Lord thank you
一旦你说主感谢你，再看一遍
you become objective and then you ask
你变得客观，然后你问
God could you be disciplining me and if
上帝你能训练我，如果
he is he will point it out if there's
他是否会指出它是否存在
something there and then you just
那里的东西然后你就是
confess it you don't dwell on that you
承认你不要纠缠于你
don't boot yourself around the barn
不要自己在谷仓里自拔
about it what good does that do you say
关于它你说的有什么好处
Lord that was sin and when you do he can
主是罪，当你做的时候他就可以
cleanses you from that and from all
洗净你从和所有
unrighteousness
不义
because you have advocate with the
因为你有倡导者
father Jesus who died in your place
在你身边死去的父亲耶稣
and so you confess that and then you
所以你承认那个然后你
take the next step well what's the next
下一步好了下一步
step well the next step oh by the way in
顺便说一下，顺便进行 下一步哦
this Hebrews 12 5 and 6 a passage that
希伯来书12 5和6这段经文
is spelled out here and you have
在这里拼写，你有
forgotten the exhortation which is
忘记了劝诫
addressed to you as sons my god do not
作为儿子，我的上帝没有给你
regard light my son do not regard
我的儿子不重视光
lightly the discipline of the Lord nor
轻轻地遵守主的纪律也不是
faint when you are reproved by him for
晕当你被他责备
those whom the Lord loves he disciplines
那些主爱他的人
and he scourges every son whom he
他鞭打他所有的儿子
received you need to remember that's
收到你需要记住那个
hope you know that's good when you say
希望你知道，当你说时，这很好
Lord could you be discipling me and you
主啊，你能训练我和你吗？
see that he is that's hope why because
看到他是那个希望为什么因为
that means he's your father
这意味着他是你的父亲
I don't discipline if it's not my kid
如果不是我的孩子，我不会自律
I might go to you know the parent and
我可能会告诉你父母和
say you realize your son is hopping over
说你意识到你的儿子正在跳过
all the pews with muddy feet and getting
所有的长椅都有泥泞的脚和得到
everything dirty and I have him deal
一切都很脏，我让他交易
with it I might speak to the child but
它我可能对孩子 说话 ，但
it's the father's duty to discipline so
这是父亲的责任，纪律，
if God is disciplining me then I must be
如果上帝训练我，那么我一定是
his kid do you know that this passage
他的孩子你知道这段话
which we didn't get to was one of the
我们没有得到的是其中之一
very encouraging passages that God used
上帝使用的非常令人鼓舞的段落
in my heart you wouldn't think so but
在我的心脏，你会这么认为，但
when I was depressed
我郁闷的时候
I felt like I was really under
我觉得自己真的很失望
discipline and when I got to this
纪律，当我到达这一点
passage I thought whoa wait a minute if
通过我认为哇等一下如果
I'm under discipline then I must be one
我在纪律之下然后我必须是一个
of his kids and he gave me hope because
他的孩子们，他给了我希望，因为
I really felt like I was under
我真的觉得我不在
discipline but this gave me hope because
纪律，但这给了我希望，因为
well then I must be his child if I'm
那么如果我是的话，我一定是他的孩子
under discipline well then the next step
在纪律下， 然后下一步
what's the next step
下一步是什么
ask what can I learn from this test how
问我可以从这个测试中学到什么
can I glorify God in this trial in
我可以在这次审判中荣耀上帝吗？
Galatians 5:22 23 but the fruit of the
加拉太书5:22 23但是果子的结果
Spirit is love joy peace patience
精神就是爱和平的耐心
kindness goodness gentleness
善良善良温柔
faithfulness and self-control against
忠诚和自制
such things there is no law oh that's
这样的事情没有法律哦那就是
too much love let's make a law now
太多的爱让我们 现在 制定法律
that's too much self-control goodnight
这是太多的自我控制晚安
the guy needs to loosen up let's make a
这家伙需要放松让我们做一个
law you know no he's too patient yeah
法律，你知道不，他太病人耶
that person is definitely too kind let's
那个人肯定太善良了
make a law you don't have to have laws
制定法律， 你没有法律
against that
针对
and you need laws against immorality we
你需要反对不道德的法律我们
got laws to regulate divorce but here's
有法律来规范离婚但这里是
the picture see as you give this back to
图片看到你回复了
God thank you Father for this trial
上帝，谢谢你父亲参加这次审判
could you be disciplining me confess
你能训练我承认吗？
that now what can I learn well the guy
那现在我能学到什么呢
is acting like a jerk can I learn how to
我是一个混蛋，我可以学习如何
love somebody who's acting like a jerk
爱一个像混蛋一样的人
can I learn about God's peace when
我什么时候才能了解上帝的平安？
somebody is acting like a jerk can I
有人像我这样的混蛋
learn about joy in the midst of a trial
在审判中了解快乐
can I learn about patience or kindness
我可以了解耐心或善意吗？
or gentleness or faithfulness or
或温柔或忠诚或
goodness or self-control or faithfulness
善良或自制或忠诚
when the guy's acting like a jerk yes
当那个家伙表现得像个混蛋一样
when I'm going through a test and I'm
当我正在进行测试时，我就是
just a lady at the school and she's only
只是学校里的一位女士而且她是唯一的
been out as far as I know to one outside
据我所知，一个外面的人
event in the last three years and she
事件在过去的三年中 ，她
suffers every day with unbelievably
每天都难以置信地受苦
serious pain but she does it for the
严重的疼痛，但她为此做了
glory of God and has an amazing
上帝的荣耀，有一个惊人的
testimony but she deals with that every
证词，但她处理每一个
day
天
so I try to make it my habit that she's
所以我尽量让我的习惯，她的
the first person I pray for when I wake
第一人称我祈祷，当我醒来
up
向上
and the night each night and I turn my
每天晚上和我转过身来
mind and I pray for her and then there's
我会为她祈祷，然后就是这样
two or three others that I know are
我认识的其他两三个人
dealing with physical pain all the time
对付身体的疼痛所有的时间
and I try to remember to pray for them
我试着记得为他们祈祷
and we reach out to someone else in your
我们联系你的其他人
situation but how will you really learn
情况， 但你将如何真正学习
the love of God if you don't face
如果你不面对，就是上帝的爱
situation that have to deal with
有处理情况
situations that cause you to be
导致你的情况
frustrated you see for God so loved the
沮丧你看到上帝如此喜爱
world that He gave His only begotten Son
世人认为他给他的独生子
and he loved those who rejected him and
他爱那些谁拒绝了他，并
he loved us while we were sinners so if
如果我们是罪人，他就爱我们
you don't have the chance to show love
你没有机会表达爱意
to someone who's sinning against you you
对某人犯了你的罪
don't have a chance to demonstrate the
没有机会展示
love of God I have no problem saying hi
对上帝的爱我没有问题
to you if you greet me and say hey Bob
如果你问候我并说嘿鲍勃
how are you doing I'm hi how you doing
你好吗我喜欢你的表现
you walk by me and you look like the
你走过我，你看起来像
Grim Reaper and you never say anything
死神， 你永远不会说什么
to me I got along without you before I
对我来说，在我之前我没有你
met you and I can get along without you
遇到了你，没有你，我可以相处
now you know I could sing that for you
现在你知道我可以为你唱歌
but I'll save you the misery okay you
但我会拯救你的痛苦好吧
know Oh rather than hey how are you
知道哦，而不是嘿，你好吗？
doing tomorrow hey how are you doing you
明天做嘿你好吗？
know but you continue Jesus put it that
知道，但你继续耶稣说
way he made it that simple if you only
如果你这么做的话，他就这么简单
greet those who greet yous what is that
迎接那些问候你的人是什么
we've got to be willing to give to the
我们必须愿意给到
person who mistreats us how does Peter
虐待我们的人彼得怎么样
put it in first Peter when he's talking
当他说话时把它放在第一个彼得
about suffering and in first Peter
关于痛苦和在第一彼得
chapter 2 listen to what he says this
第2章 听他说的这个
was you know if you want some conviction
如果你想要一些信念 ，你知道吗？
here it is servants be submissive to
这里是仆人顺从的
your masters with all respect not only
你的主人与所有尊重不仅
to those who are good and gentle but
那些谁是善良温和的，但
also to those who are unreasonable for
对那些不合理的人也是如此
this finds favor if for the sake of your
如果为了你的利益，这会受到青睐
conscience toward God a person bears up
一个人对上帝的良心承受
under sorrows when suffering unjustly
在遭受不公正的痛苦时
because of your conscience toward God
因为你对上帝的良心
you treat me like dirt
你如何对待我如粪土
and I treat you with respect and with
我尊敬地对待你
kindness and with goodness we are to
我们要善良和善良
respond in that way so if you look at
如果你看一下，就这样回应
the outline that you have you have
你拥有的大纲
studying for example in Psalms 50 14:23
例如在Psalms 5014:23中学习
54 6 the sacrifice of praise and then
54 6 然后赞美牺牲
compare that with the passages in James
将其与詹姆斯的段落进行比较
you might even want to add in there the
你甚至可能想在那里添加
Hebrews passage let's see 12 15 if I'm
如果我是的话，希伯来书的段落让我们看到12 15
remembering correctly where it says you
记得正确地记得它在哪里
know one of the the sacrifices of a New
知道一个新的牺牲之一
Testament priest is your lips giving
遗嘱牧师是你的嘴唇
praise to Jesus all day long see what
整天赞美耶稣看什么
our trials what are all those little
我们的试验是那些小的
tests
测试
that's God's alarm clock going up time
这是上帝闹钟上升的时间
to praise me again you know traffic is
再次赞美我，你知道交通
slowed down Oh time to praise me alarm
放慢脚步哦时间来赞美我的警报
clock the the light you got caught at
把你被捕的光照亮
the light again no praise God you know
光再次没有赞美上帝，你知道
that's little alarm clocks going off all
那些小闹钟响了
day long to turn our hearts toward
一整天都把我们的心转向
praise that's why that book 31 days of
赞美这就是为什么那本书31天的原因
praise really good she deals with that
赞美真的很好， 她处理那个
in a great way and they Bailey's a book
在很棒的方式，他们贝利是一本书
also does so ask the question then
也这样问这个问题
what's the greatest trial you're facing
你面临的最大的考验是什么？
define it in a sentence in prayer give a
在一个句子中祈祷定义它 给予
sacrifice of praise thanking God for
牺牲赞美感谢上帝
that trial and then list as many ways as
该试验然后列出尽可能多的方式
you can of how God could use that trial
你可以了解上帝如何使用这个审判
for good and seek Him in the midst of it
为善，在其中寻求祂
and then walk with him through it God is
然后和他一起走过去
in control he could have prevented this
在控制中， 他本可以阻止这一点
trial but he didn't know grumbling by
审判， 但他不知道抱怨
the way I began consciously in 1971 to
我在1971年有意识地开始的方式
memorize James chapter one and to put
记住詹姆斯第一章并提出
this into practice in my life and I'm
这在我的生活中实践，我
still working on it every once in a
仍处于工作它的每一次
while I get it right and instead of
而我得到它的权利，而不是和
saying bummer
说糟糕
I say well thank you lord I know you're
我说得很好，谢谢你， 主，我知道你
at work what do you want to teach me how
在工作中你想教我怎么样？
can I grow and I do it automatically
我可以成长，我会自动完成
without having to confess the grumbling
不必承认抱怨
but I but
但我却
you know I don't know maybe once out of
你知道我不知道也许曾经出过
90 you know that I I get it right first
90你知道我先把它弄好了
without grumbling and then I have to
没有抱怨然后我必须
confess the grumbling and then we move
承认抱怨，然后我们移动
through the next step I'm working on one
通过下一步我工作的一个
of the first illustrations or them
第一个插图或他们
sitting in my office right after I
我之后就坐在办公室里
started practice back in 71 yeah that's
71岁开始练习，是的
a long time ago okay
很久以前没关系
I mean I'm slow learner all right you
我的意思是我缓慢的学习者一切顺利，
just so you know okay and I'm sitting at
只是这样你就知道了，我正坐在那里
my desk in my office and I got this big
我的办公桌在我的办公室，我得到了这么大
old desk
旧桌子
you know this yay long and just about
你知道这很久很久
that wide and I go to get some paper out
那么宽，我去拿一些纸
of this drawer and it's stuck and I
这个抽屉里的，它卡住了我
can't open it and I've had this desk for
无法打开它，我已经有了这张桌子
a year and it's always stuck when I want
一年，它总是卡在我想要的时候
to get in there anyways but otherwise it
无论如何进入那里，否则它
opens fine and so I'm pulling on the
打开罚款，所以我拉动
drawer and I stupid drawer more open
抽屉和我愚蠢的抽屉更开放
again I can't believe this it makes me
再一次，我无法相信这让我感动
so frustrated hi Donna and then I okay
唐娜这么沮丧，然后我没关系
Lord I'm grumbling it seems so stupid
主啊，我抱怨它似乎是如此愚蠢
though to thank you for the dumb drawer
虽然要感谢你的哑抽屉
that won't open I don't understand this
那不会打开我不明白这一点
and how does this really relate and this
这与真正的关系如何？
is not a big deal well then you know the
你知道的并不是什么大不了的事
thoughts why are you making it a big
想你为什么要把它变成一个大的
deal just say thank you and then ask you
交易只是说谢谢然后问你
are you disciplining me and ask what you
你在训练我，问你是什么
can learn well can I help you patients
可以好好学习，我可以帮助你的病人
yes can it help you with some
是的它可以帮助你一些
self-control yes could it help you with
自我控制是的，它可以帮助你
some joy yes could it help you with some
一些快乐是的它可以帮助你一些
peace yes okay all right so okay thank
和平是没事没事没事这么感谢
you Lord and still won't open so I went
你是主，仍然不会打开，所以我去了
out and the other office got some paper
出来，另一个办公室得到了一些文件
and came back to work next night I'm
我是第二天晚上回来工作的
working without oh Anderson in the
在没有安德森的情况下工作
office and we're working on a project
办公室，我们正在从事的项目
he's one of the elders and so he says
他是长老之一，所以他说
hey if you got some scrap paper let's do
嘿，如果你有一些废纸让我们这样做
a pros and cons list and I said oh yeah
一个利弊名单，我说哦是的
sure I'll get some paper cuz I go pull
我肯定会得到一些纸张，因为我会拉
on the drawer yeah and then I guess
在抽屉上是啊然后我猜
funny and he says what's funny I said
好笑，他说我说的有趣
the drawer no he said that's funny
抽屉没有他说这很有趣
I said well you have to understand the
我说得好，你必须明白
context so I took five minutes and I
因此我花了五分钟和我
explained to him you know what I've
向他解释你知道我的意思
explained to you and he says aha yeah
给你解释，他说啊哈啊
I'm glad the Lord's teaching you want me
我很高兴主教导你想要我
to tell you how to open the drawer I
告诉你如何打开抽屉我
said yeah and he said open the center
说是的，他说打开中心
drawer I pull the center drawer open he
抽屉我拉中心抽屉打开他
said now open the side door I opened the
说现在打开我开的侧门
side rooms
侧房
I said honor your genius how you know
我说尊敬你的天才你怎么知道
this yeah I've got a desk like that down
这是的，我有一张像这样的桌子
into the office it's broken the locks
进入办公室它打破了锁
broken on that desk isn't that so yeah
在桌子上打破的不是那么好
how'd you know that he said well because
你怎么知道他说得好，因为
that's what happens it breaks and it
这就是发生了什么，它打破了它
breaks in the locked position but you
在锁定的位置打破， 但你
can still pull the senator are open when
仍然可以拉参议员开放的时候
you pull the senator drove and it
你拉参议员开车了
releases the lever in the back which is
释放后部的杠杆
pushed against the lever that locks that
推开锁定它的杠杆
drawer so whenever you push the center
抽屉， 所以每当你推动中心
drawer in a little too far it engages
抽屉有点太过分了
that lever in the back and locks the
那个杠杆在后面并锁定
side drawer I said oh yeah push this one
侧抽屉我说哦是的推这一个
in locked pull this one out
在锁定拉这一个
unlock push this one in locked you know
解锁推这个锁定你知道
sometimes God works out the problem just
有时上帝只是解决问题
that quick when you finally say thank
当你最后说谢谢时，那很快
you okay
你没事
not always though but the idea is when
并非总是如此， 但这个想法是什么时候
we by faith say thank you what does
我们凭信心说谢谢你做了什么
Hebrews 11:6 say without faith it's
希伯来书11：6毫无信心地说
impossible to please him when you
不可能你什么时候请他
exercise faith by offering the sacrifice
通过提供牺牲来运用信仰
of Thanksgiving and ask God what he
感恩节，问上帝他是什么
wants you to t what he wants to teach
想要你想要教他的东西
you it brings a great joy as we work
你工作的时候会带来很大的快乐
through trials together and it's
通过一起试验，它是
important if the serious trial is you're
如果你是严肃的审判，这很重要
paraplegic read Johnny's original
截瘫阅读Johnny的原创
testimony in the book Johnny and she
约翰尼和她的书中的见证
will tell you that when she said thank
当她说谢谢时会告诉你
you God began to work sovereignly to
你上帝开始主权地工作了
show her what he was going to do through
向她展示他将要做的事情
that trial so let's close him but let me
那次审判让我们关闭他，但让我
share one other thought with regard to
与...分享另一个想法
Johnny I had the privilege of hurrying
约翰尼我有幸匆忙赶来
here hearing her one of the first time
在这里听到她的第一次
she shared her testimony back in New
她在新的时候分享了她的见证
Jersey
新泽西
three thousand seat auditorium balcony
三千个座位的礼堂阳台
we're on the back row of the balcony up
我们在阳台的后排
against the wall and she's down on the
靠在墙上，她倒在了
platform in her wheelchair giving her
在轮椅上给她的平台
testimony she ended it this way she said
她以这种方式结束了她的证词
wouldn't it be a marvelous thing if
如果这不是一件奇妙的事情
tonight God healed me miraculously I
今晚神奇迹般地医治了我
leaped up out of my wheelchair I ran
从我的轮椅上跳起来， 我跑了
down the aisle I threw my arms around
沿着过道我搂着我
you and I hugged you that would be the
你和我拥抱你会是那样的
first person I've hugged in ten years
我十年来第一个拥抱的人
would that be amazing
那太棒了
well kind of yeah that would be amazing
很好，是的，这将是惊人的
now she said isn't it even more amazing
现在，她说，是不是更令人称奇
that I can sit here
我可以坐在这里
in this wheelchair and tell you that the
在这个轮椅上，并告诉你
grace of God is sufficient and that His
上帝的恩典足够和他的
grace is sufficient and I wouldn't
恩惠是足够的，我不会
change anything and she tipped her head
改变一切，她低下头
to decide and she began to sing Amazing
决定，她开始唱神奇
Grace how sweet the sound that saved a
恩惠是多么甜蜜的声音，拯救了一个
wretch like me and you know there
像我一样的坏蛋，你知道那里
weren't too many dry eyes in the
眼睛没有太多干眼
auditorium and I know mine weren't and
礼堂，我知道我的不是和
that's a long time ago and she still
很久以前，她还在
sits in that chair proclaims the truth
坐在那把椅子上宣告真相
of God and the trials she's been through
上帝和她经历的考验
in the last few years she says have
在过去的几年里，她说有
really been more difficult and you know
真的变得更加困难，你知道
what she said in a New World magazine
她在“新世界”杂志上所说的话
interview so I just want to be faithful
面试所以我只想忠实
I don't want to do anything that would
我不想做任何会
bring dishonor to the name of my Savior
给我救主的名字带来羞辱
may God give us that kind of spirit in
愿上帝赐给我们那种精神
our trials
我们的试验
you
您